Guide to the Victor F. Germack and Lori Shepard Germack Collection of Photographs of Indians of North America
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Postcards, circa 1900-1978; Series VII; 1; (1 box)
  - Photomechanical Postcards
    - Detroit Photographic Company
      - Moki Indian Cigarette Smoker (No. 244 and No. 5255), circa 1899; (3 postcards) (Box 17, Folder 1170-1172)
      - Pueblo of Acoma and Mesa Encantada, New Mexico (No. 5509), circa 1900 (Box 17, Folder 1173)
      - A Navajo Blanket Weaver (No. 5510), 1901 (Box 17, Folder 1174)
      - Old Carreta, Laguna Pueblo, New Mexico (No. 5885), circa 1900 (Box 17, Folder 1175)
      - Taqui, a Hopi (Moki) Snake Priest (No. 5886), 1902 (Box 17, Folder 1176-1178)
      - A Pima Papoose (No. 6091); a Pima Indian Infant in a Cradleboard, circa 1900 (Box 17, Folder 1179)
      - Papago Indian Woman Filling the Olla (No. 6506), 1903 (Box 17, Folder 1180)
      - Pueblo Indians Selling Pottery (No. 6848); Pueblo Indian Women Selling Pottery on a Railroad Depot Platform, 1902 (Box 17, Folder 1181)
      - A Proud Mother (No. 6880); an American Indian Woman with an Infant in a Cradleboard, 1903 (Box 17, Folder 1182)
      - Chief Paupuk Keewis (No. 6883); European American Man Wearing American Indian Regalia and Portraying a Character of Pau-Puk-Keewis in The Song of Hiawatha by Henry Wadsworth Longfellow, 1903 (Box 17, Folder 1183)
      - Brothers in Exile (No. 6888): Two American Indian Infants in Cradleboards, 1903 (Box 17, Folder 1184)
      - The Hopi House, Grand Canyon of Arizona (No. 7991), circa 1905 (Box 17, Folder 1185)
      - A Character in Yosemite Valley, California (No. 8413); American Indian Woman, circa 1905 (Box 17, Folder 1186)
      - Entrance to Navaho Blanket Collection, Albuquerque, New Mexico (No. 9901), circa 1905 (Box 17, Folder 1187)
        Original image copyrighted by the Fred Harvey Company.
      - A Cute Little Apache (No. 12221); an Apache Indian Woman with an Infant in a Cradleboard, circa 1900 (Box 17, Folder 1188)
      - Montera Cabezon, Apache Indian Man, Arizona (No. 13941), circa 1900 (Box 17, Folder 1189)
      - A Scene at the Pueblo of Santo Domingo, New Mexico (No. 79217); Three American Indian Children on a Ladder at the Kewa Pueblo, New Mexico, circa 1900 (Box 17, Folder 1190)
      - First Santa Fe Train (No. H-1916); Drawing of Nine American Indian Men, Most on Horseback, Looking at a Train in the Distance after a painting by Frank Paul Sauerwein, circa 1920 (Box 17, Folder 1191)
      - Hopi Snake Dance, Arizona (No. H-2071), circa 1920 (Box 17, Folder 1192)
      - Pueblo of Zuni, New Mexico (No. H-2236), circa 1920 (Box 17, Folder 1193)
    - E. C. Kropp Company
      - Black Eagle, American Indian Man (No. 272), circa 1901 (Box 17, Folder 1194)
      - Native Floridians, Palmetto House (No. 1621), circa 1906 (Box 17, Folder 1195)
      - Indian Squaw and Papoose; an American Indian Woman with an Infant in a Cradleboard, circa 1910 (Box 17, Folder 1196)
    - E. Frey and Company
      - Gall (Phizí), Teton Indian Man (No. 2387), circa 1905 (Box 17, Folder 1197)
    - Fawcett, Waldon
      - Peter Tall Mandan, Dakota Indian, circa 1905 (Box 17, Folder 1198)
      - White Tail, Ponca Indian Man, 1906 (Box 17, Folder 1199)
    - Fred Harvey (Firm)
      - Elle Weaving, Indian Building, Albuquerque, New Mexico, 1904 (Box 17, Folder 1200)
      - A Group of Navahoes, Albuquerque, New Mexico (No. 7945), circa 1905 (Box 17, Folder 1201)
      - The Indian and Mexican Building, Albuquerque, New Mexico (No. 7946), 1906 (Box 17, Folder 1202)
      - Main Rooms, Hopi House, Grand Canyon of Arizona (No. 7988), circa 1906 (Box 17, Folder 1203)
      - Old Blanket Room in Hopi House, Grand Canyon of Arizona (No. 7993), circa 1906 (Box 17, Folder 1204)
      - An Indian Living Room, Hopi House, Grand Canyon of Arizona (No. 9286), circa 1908 (Box 17, Folder 1205)
      - Elle of Ganado, Acknowledged the Best Weaver Among the Navahoes (No. 9996), 1908 (Box 17, Folder 1206)
      - Elle of Ganado. Maker of the President's Blanket. The Best Weaver Among the Navahoes (No. 9999), 1908; (2 postcards) (Box 17, Folder 1207)
      - Juana Marie, a Pueblo Indian of Isleta, Indian Building, Albuquerque, New Mexico, circa 1908 (Box 17, Folder 1208)
        Original photograph created by Karl Everton Moon in 1906.
      - Old Mojave Indian Woman on the Desert Near Needles, California, circa 1909 (Box 17, Folder 1209)
    - Gies and Company
      - Doe-Wah-Jack Seeking New Hunting Grounds, circa 1911 (Box 17, Folder 1210)
        Published to advertise Round Oak Stoves manufactured by P. D. Beckwith Incorporated, Dowagiac, Michigan.
    - Gilpin, Laura
      Printed by the Meriden Gravure Company.
      Postcards created for sets in the series Pictorial Post Cards of the Southwest.
      - Envelope for Pictorial Post Cards of the Southwest, Set No. 7, El Santuario De Chimayó, circa 1945 (Box 17, Folder 1211)
      - El Santuario De Chimayó, New Mexico, circa 1945 (Box 17, Folder 1212)
      - El Santuario De Chimayó, New Mexico, Variant View, circa 1945 (Box 17, Folder 1213)
      - Churchyard, El Santuario De Chimayó, New Mexico, circa 1945 (Box 17, Folder 1214)
      - Old Carved Door, El Santuario De Chimayó, New Mexico, circa 1945 (Box 17, Folder 1215-1216)
      - Interior, El Santuario De Chimayó, New Mexico, circa 1945 (Box 17, Folder 1217)
      - Navahos by Firelight, circa 1945 (Box 17, Folder 1218)
      - Navaho Girl, circa 1945 (Box 17, Folder 1219)
      - Navaho Indian Woman, circa 1945 (Box 17, Folder 1220-1221)
      - Navaho Summer Hogan, circa 1945 (Box 17, Folder 1222)
      - Shepherds of the Desert, circa 1945 (Box 17, Folder 1223)
      - Sun Temple, Mesa Verde National Park, circa 1945 (Box 17, Folder 1224)
      - Round Tower at Cliff Palace, Mesa Verde National Park, circa 1945 (Box 17, Folder 1225)
      - Taos Indian Woman, Taos Pueblo, circa 1945 (Box 17, Folder 1226)
      - The White Sheet, also known as Taos Pueblo Indian, Taos Pueblo, circa 1945 (Box 17, Folder 1227)
      - Church, Taos Pueblo, circa 1945 (Box 17, Folder 1228)
      - Arab of the American Desert, Taos Pueblo, circa 1945 (Box 17, Folder 1229)
      - Kiva, San Ildefonso Pueblo, New Mexico, circa 1945 (Box 17, Folder 1230-1231)
    - H. H. Tammen Company
      - Chief Red Cloud (No. 202), 1903 (Box 17, Folder 1232)
      - Indian Papoose (No. 204); American Indian Infant in a Cradleboard, 1903 (Box 17, Folder 1233)
      - Getting Ready for the Pow Wow (No. 205); Group of American Indians, 1903 (Box 17, Folder 1234)
      - Cupid on the Warpath (No. 206); Drawing of Seven American Indian Children and a Rabbit, 1903 (Box 17, Folder 1235)
      - An Indian Warrior (No. 208), circa 1905 (Box 17, Folder 1236)
      - Hopi Indian Man Weaving Blanket, Oraibi, Arizona (No. 607), circa 1905 (Box 17, Folder 1237)
      - Wolf Robe (Tsitsistas or Suhtai), Cheyenne Indian Man, circa 1905 (Box 17, Folder 1238)
      - In Hopiland (No. 5731); Two Hopi Indian Women and Two Hopi Indian Children, circa 1920 (Box 17, Folder 1239)
      - Famous Indian Chiefs, Souvenir Folder, circa 1935 (Box 17, Folder 1240)
        Outside of the folder includes images of Chief Red Cloud (recto) and Hitting The Trail - Chief Three Bears and Squaw (verso).
        Inside of the folder text discusses American Indian Chiefs.
        Fanfold views in the folder include: Chief Hollow Horn Bear; Juan Pedro Navajo; Chief Red Cloud; A Navajo; Chief Wolf Robe; Chief Geronimo; Chief Eagle Feather; Chief Spotted Tail; Chief Sitting Bull; Chief Black Bird; The Medicine Lodge - Glacier National Park, Montana; Blackfeet Warriors at Cut Bank Canyon - Glacier National Park; Hitting The Trail - Chief Three Bears and Squaw; Chief Three Bears - oldest resident of Glacier National Park, Montana; Vincenti - Chief of All the Navajos; Chief Two Guns White Calf - Blackfeet Indian - Glacier Nationa Park; Tom of Cochiti; Lazy Boy - Old Blackfeet Indian Warrior and Hunter; Medicine Owl - Blackfeet Medicine Man - Glacier National Park; and Chief Thunderbird.
    - Hampton's Magazine
      - A Little Arctic Maid, North Pole Gravure Series; an American Indian Girl, 1909-1910 (Box 17, Folder 1241)
    - Heal, W. S.
      - You, Why Don't You Write?; Drawing of an American Indian Man Holding a Bottle, circa 1906 (Box 17, Folder 1242)
        Postcard printed on leather.
    - Hotel Ansley
      - Painting in the Hotel Ansley, Atlanta, Georgia, of John Wesley Teaching the Indians Under the Oaks of Saint Simons, 1736, circa 1914 (Box 17, Folder 1243)
    - Huffman, Laton Alton
      - Good Eye, Crow Indian Man, in 1880, 1907 (Box 17, Folder 1244)
    - Illustrated Postal Card Company
      - American Indian Man (No. 77-10), circa 1900-1910 (Box 17, Folder 1245)
      - Five American Indian Men (No. 77-11), circa 1900-1910 (Box 17, Folder 1246)
      - Aupoakte Win. Kills Morning Squaw and Papoose (No. 77-34), circa 1900-1910 (Box 17, Folder 1247-1248)
    - Inland Printing Company
      - Native American, Spokane, Washington; an American Indian Woman with an Infant in a Cradleboard, circa 1900 (Box 17, Folder 1249)
    - J. Valentine and Co.
      - Indian Children, Canadian Section, Coronation Exhibition, London, 1911 (Box 17, Folder 1250)
    - John F. Byrnes and Company
      - Black Fox or Joe Black Fox (Strigi-Sapa) and Iron Tail (Sinte Maza), Oglala Indian Men (No. 7), 1901 (Box 17, Folder 1251)
        Original photograph by E. J. Freiberg.
    - John Wanamaker (Firm)
      - Flat Head Woman, American Indian Man, Dressed for War Dance, 1909 (Box 17, Folder 1252)
    - Mitchell, Edward H.
      - Sutter's Fort, Sacramento, California, Before Restoration (No. 27), circa 1905 (Box 17, Folder 1253)
      - Yava Supalt Indian Squaw and Papoose (No. 117), circa 1905 (Box 17, Folder 1254)
      - Seattle (Si'ahl), Chief of the Duwamish and Suquamish Indians (No. 660), circa 1905 (Box 17, Folder 1255)
      - American Indians, Little Soldier (Wa-non'-she-zhin-ga), Ponca Indian Man (No. 1538), circa 1905 (Box 17, Folder 1256)
      - Five Little Eskimo Sisters (No. 1998), 1905 (Box 17, Folder 1257)
        Original photograph by Frank H. Nowell.
    - Morris, Charles E.
      - Plains Indians and Teepee. Cree Tribe (No. M3000 and No. A34749), circa 1907 (Box 17, Folder 1258)
    - Musa Isle
      - Seminole Indian Family Group at the Musa Isle Indian Village, Miami, Florida (No. M-44 and C-H1175), 1950 (Box 17, Folder 1259)
        Probably printed by the Teich Company.
    - Museum of the American Indian
      - Eastern Chippewa Matriarch, circa 1900 (No. 219C), 1977 (Box 17, Folder 1260)
      - Blackfeet Indian Woman, circa 1900 (No. 1219S), 1977 (Box 17, Folder 1261)
      - Sits Before a Cloud, Crow Indian Man, circa 1900 (No. 1364S), 1977 (Box 17, Folder 1262)
    - Newman Postcard Company
      - Scene in Santa Clara Pueblo Indian Village, Near Santa Fe, New Mexico; Indian Dancers at the Santa Clara Indian Reservation, Near Santa Fe, New Mexico, circa 1909 (Box 17, Folder 1263)
        Published for Stripling Burrows and Company, Santa Fe, New Mexico.
      - Old Indian Woman (No. A.C. 13 and No. 62248), circa 1910 (Box 17, Folder 1264)
      - Pima Indian Woman and Baskets (No. A.C. 16), circa 1910 (Box 17, Folder 1265)
    - O. H. Brown and Company
      - Mary Selmore, Passamaquoddy Indian, Aged 101 Years, Near Eastport, Maine (No. 11059), circa 1906 (Box 17, Folder 1266-1267)
    - Pacific Novelty Company
      - Indians Washing Clothes in Hot Springs at Steamboat, Nevada (No. 381), circa 1910 (Box 17, Folder 1268)
      - Indian and Papoose (No. 382), circa 1910 (Box 17, Folder 1269)
    - Petley Studios
      - Laguna Indian Dog Dancers, circa 1960 (Box 17, Folder 1270)
        Photograph courtesy of the Santa Fe Railway.
    - Porte Company
      - Sioux Indians, North Dakota, circa 1907 (Box 17, Folder 1271)
    - Porteous and Mitchell Company
      - William F. "Buffalo Bill" Cody and American Indians from his Wild West Show at the Monument to Chief Uncas at the Royal Mohegan Burial Ground, Norwich, Connecticut, on July 2, 1907, 1909 (Box 17, Folder 1272)
    - Prudential Insurance Company of America
      - Hopi Indians; Hopi Indian Man and Two Hopi Indian Women In and Around an Adobe Structure, circa 1905 (Box 17, Folder 1273)
        Original image from a stereograph by Underwood & Underwood, 1902.
      - Navajo Indians at Breakfast; Two Navajo Indian Women and a Navajo Indian Man Sitting on the Ground by a Wickiup, circa 1905 (Box 17, Folder 1274)
    - Raphael Tuck and Sons
      - Hiawatha, Series I
        Portraits of unidentified American Indian men by Cavendish Morton with quotes from The Song of Hiawatha by Henry Wadsworth Longfellow
        - "Never any deed of daring.. .", circa 1904 (Box 17, Folder 1275-1276)
        - "From his forehead fell his tresses.. .", circa 1904 (Box 17, Folder 1277)
        - "Streaked with crimson, blue, and yellow.. .", circa 1904 (Box 17, Folder 1278-1279)
        - "Tall of stature, broad of shoulder.. .", circa 1904 (Box 17, Folder 1280)
        - "On his head his eagle feathers.. .", circa 1904 (Box 17, Folder 1281)
        - "Wampum belts, and strings and pouches.. .", circa 1904 (Box 17, Folder 1282)
      - Hiawatha, Series II
        - "On his head his eagle feathers.. .", circa 1905 (Box 17, Folder 1283)
      - Indian Chiefs, Series II
        Original photographs probably by De Lancey W. Gill in Washington, D.C., March 1905.
        - Black Chicken, Yankton Indian Man, circa 1905 (Box 17, Folder 1284)
        - Iron Owl, Yankton Indian Man, circa 1905 (Box 17, Folder 1285)
        - Not Afraid of Pawnee, Yankton Indian Man, circa 1905 (Box 17, Folder 1286)
        - Red Owl, Yankton Indian Man, circa 1905 (Box 17, Folder 1287)
        - Stranger Horse, Yankton Indian Man, circa 1905 (Box 17, Folder 1288)
        - White Swan or Joseph H. Ellis, Jr. (Maga Ska), Yankton Indian Man, circa 1905 (Box 17, Folder 1289)
    - Rieder, M.
      - The Real Ramona (No. 504), circa 1910 (Box 17, Folder 1290)
    - Rinehart, Frank Albert, and Adolph F. Muhr
      Photographs created by Adolph F. Muhr at the Trans-Mississippi Exposition in Omaha, Nebraska, in 1898, and copyrighted by his employer, Frank Albert Rinehart, as well as photographs created elsewhere. Rinehart issued three series of six postcards from 1903-1905.
      - 1903
        - Bill Rock, Crow Indian Man, 1903 (Box 17, Folder 1291-1292)
        - Big Man, American Indian Man, 1903 (Box 17, Folder 1293-1294)
        - Chase in the Morning, Oglala Indian Man, 1903 (Box 17, Folder 1295-1296)
        - Clear, American Indian Man, 1903 (Box 17, Folder 1297)
        - Wolf Robe (Tsitsistas or Suhtai), Cheyenne Indian Man, 1903 (Box 17, Folder 1298)
        - Yellow Wolf (Sunkazi), Oglala Indian Man, 1903 (Box 17, Folder 1299-1301)
      - 1904
        - Rain in the Face (Ité Omágažu, Iromagaja, or Itonagaju), a Dakota Indian Man, 1904 (Box 17, Folder 1302-1304)
        - Eagle Feather and Papoose, Dakota Indian Woman and Dakota Indian Girl, 1904 (Box 17, Folder 1305)
        - Sitting Bull (Thatháŋka Íyotake), a Hunkpapa Indian Man, 1904 (Box 17, Folder 1306)
        - Red Cloud or Scarlet Cloud (Makhpiya-luta, Mahpina Luta), Oglala Indian Man, 1904 (Box 17, Folder 1307)
      - 1905
        - Little Bear and White Bull, Dakota Indian Infants, 1905 (Box 17, Folder 1308)
        - Two Little Braves, Sac and Fox Indian Boys, 1905 (Box 17, Folder 1309)
        - Lost Bird, Dakota Indian Girl, 1905 (Box 17, Folder 1310)
        - Sioux Squaw and Papoose; Dakota Indian Woman, and Lost Bird, Dakota Indian Girl, 1905 (Box 17, Folder 1311)
        - Wah-Ta-Waso, Iroquois Indian Woman, 1905 (Box 17, Folder 1312)
        - Annie Red Shirt, Dakota Indian Woman, 1905 (Box 17, Folder 1313)
    - Selige, Adoph
      - Bear Goes in the Wood, American Indian Man, circa 1905 (Box 17, Folder 1314-1315)
      - Collection of Baskets Made by Indians (No. 2839), circa 1910 (Box 17, Folder 1316)
      - Town Chief's Weha's House (No. 3601), Home of Chief Weha, Masset Band of the Haida Tribe in British Columbia, circa 1910 (Box 17, Folder 1317)
      - Wanita (Juanita) Redbird, American Indian Woman, circa 1905 (Box 17, Folder 1318)
    - Souvenir Publishing Company
      - Paiute Papooses (No. 2907); Two Paiute Indian Infants in Cradleboards, circa 1900 (Box 17, Folder 1319)
    - Spokane Post Card Company
      - Me and Joe Opened the Flathead Reservation, Missoula, Montana; Joseph Moore Dixon with an American Indian Woman and an American Indian Man, circa 1909 (Box 17, Folder 1320)
        Phrase on postcard refers to the sale of land on the Flathead Indian Reservation made possible by Senator Joseph Moore Dixon
    - T. H. Hall's Colonial Book Store
      - Melicite Indian Wigwam, St. John River, circa 1910 (Box 17, Folder 1321)
    - Teich Company
      - Morning Greetings, Isleta Indians, Isleta Pueblo, Near Albuquerque, New Mexico (No. A-33992); Two Isleta Indian Women and an Isleta Indian Girl, 1913; (2 postcards) (Box 17, Folder 1322-1323)
        One postcard published for Joseph Roy "J. R." Willis.
      - Corn Dance, Pueblo of Santo Domingo, New Mexico; American Indian Corn Dancers at the Kewa Pueblo, New Mexico, 1913 (Box 17, Folder 1324)
      - Indian Family Pueblo of Cochiti, New Mexico (No. 34043), 1913 (Box 17, Folder 1325)
        Published for Strong's Book Store, Albuquerque, New Mexico.
      - Typical Zuni Pueblo Indians, Boy and Grandmother (No. 66 and A-34046), 1913 (Box 17, Folder 1326)
      - Hopi Snake Dance (No. 34064), 1913; (3 postcards) (Box 17, Folder 1327-1329)
        Original painting created by C. W. Warton James.
        One postcard published for Henry Herz, San Diego, California.
        Two postcards published for Joseph Roy "J. R." Willis.
      - Children of the Pueblo Indians Learning to Dance (No. 34071), 1913 (Box 17, Folder 1330)
      - Women of Tesuque Pueblo, New Mexico (No. 51121-C); Four Tewa Indian Women, and Two Tewa Indian Children, 1914 (Box 17, Folder 1331)
        Published for Southwest Arts and Crafts, Santa Fe, New Mexico.
      - Indian Camp on Miller Brothers 101 Ranch, Oklahoma (No. 78996), 1919 (Box 17, Folder 1332)
      - Pueblo Indian Dancers, Gallup, New Mexico (No. 2237-30), 1930 (Box 17, Folder 1333)
      - Apache Indians (No. 4A-H920), 1934 (Box 17, Folder 1334)
      - Pueblo Indian Maid (No. 4A-H1131), 1934 (Box 17, Folder 1335)
        Published for Henry Herz, San Diego, California.
      - Choctaw Indian Princess, Oklahoma (No. 6B-H2185), 1946 (Box 17, Folder 1336)
        Published for the Oklahoma City Chamber of Commerce.
      - Famous Indian Papoose Twins (No. 7A-H1564); Two Cayuse Indian Infants in Cradleboards, 1937 (Box 17, Folder 1337)
        Original photograph created by Thomas Leander "Lee" Moorhouse in 1898.
      - Devil Dance of the Apache Indians (No. 7A-H2241), 1937 (Box 17, Folder 1338)
        Published for Southwest Post Card Company, Albuquerque, New Mexico.
      - Apache Indians in Camp, New Mexico and Arizona (No. 7A-H3352), 1937 (Box 17, Folder 1339)
        Published for Joseph Roy "J. R." Willis.
      - Apache Ghost Dancers (No. 8A88-N, 1938 (Box 17, Folder 1340)
        Published for Mid-Continent News Company, Oklahoma City, Oklahoma.
      - Whirling Log (Good Luck) Sand Painting of the Navajo Indians (No. 9A-H805), 1939 (Box 17, Folder 1341)
      - Pueblo Indian Corn Dance (No. OB-H213), 1946 (Box 17, Folder 1342)
      - Mother and Daughter Baking Bread, circa 1970 (Box 17, Folder 1343)
        Original photograph by the New Mexico Department of Development.
        Published for the Southwest Post Card Company, Albuquerque, New Mexico.
      - The Land of Sky Blue Waters, Northwest Indians (No. 175 and OB-H88), 1940 (Box 17, Folder 1344)
        Published for Wesley Andrews Company, Portland, Oregon.
      - A Typical Indian Home in the Southwest (No. D-46 and No. OB-H2718, 1940 (Box 17, Folder 1345)
        Published for Lollesgard Specialty Company, Tucson, Arizona.
      - Little Papago Girl Carrying Water, Showing Olla in a Burden Basket (No. I-25 and No. 3B-H1375), 1943 (Box 17, Folder 1346)
        Original photograph by Chuck Abbott.
        Published for Lollesgard Specialty Company, Tucson, Arizona
      - Seminole Indians, Miami, Florida; Identifies Jack Tiger Tail, a Seminole Indian Man Killed in 1922 at Coppinger's Tropical Gardens in Miami, Florida (No. A-51658), 1914 (Box 17, Folder 1347)
        Published for J. N. Chamberlain, Miami, Florida.
    - Thayer Publishing Company
      - Mount of the Holy Cross, Colorado (No. 704), circa 1908 (Box 17, Folder 1348)
      - Men or Women, Which? (No. 753), circa 1913 (Box 17, Folder 1349)
      - Zuni Indian Basket Weaver (No. 760), circa 1910 (Box 17, Folder 1350)
      - Taos Indians (No. 1566); Two Taos Indian Men on Horseback, circa 1910 (Box 17, Folder 1351)
    - Tichnor Brothers
      - How Navajo Rugs are Made (No. G42 and 69445), circa 1935 (Box 17, Folder 1352)
      - A Seminole Family Group (No. 106), circa 1935 (Box 17, Folder 1353)
    - V.O. Hammon Publishing Company
      - Running Wolf, Brulé Indian Man (No. 153), circa 1900-1910 (Box 17, Folder 1354)
    - Valentine-Souvenir Company
      - Indians on Allegany River, Near Salamanca, New York, circa 1915 (Box 17, Folder 1355)
    - W. J. Gage and Company
      - Setukkomuccon, Sarsi Indian Man (No. 3299), circa 1906 (Box 17, Folder 1356)
    - Walter M. Lowney Company
      - Drawing of an American Indian Man (No. 1), 1906 (Box 17, Folder 1357)
        Premium postcard for Lowney's Chocolates.
    - Warwick Bros. & Rutter
      - Copper Head Chief (No. 5000), circa 1900 (Box 17, Folder 1358)
      - Running Wolf (No. 5002), circa 1900 (Box 17, Folder 1359)
    - Weltmer, Jacob
      - Indian Dance, Santa Clara Indian Reservation, Near Santa Fe, New Mexico (No. 5239), circa 1910 (Box 17, Folder 1360)
    - Williamson-Hafner Company
      - A Hopi Woman in Wedding Dress, Oraibi. On Santa Fe Railroad (No. 616), circa 1907 (Box 17, Folder 1361)
      - Alkali Ike, The Boss of the Herd (No. 1730), From a Painting by F. W. Schultz, 1907 (Box 17, Folder 1362)
      - Crossing the Rio Grande, Del Norte (No. 1747); Five American Indian Men on Horseback in the Rio Grande, 1907 (Box 17, Folder 1363)
      - Standing Wolf, Cheyenne Indian Man (No. 1611), From a Painting by F. W. Schultz, circa 1908 (Box 17, Folder 1364)
      - Red Cloud, Oglala Indian Man (No. 1618), From a Painting by F. W. Schultz, circa 1908 (Box 17, Folder 1365)
    - Unidentified Photographer or Publisher
      - Hot Meals at All Hours; an American Indian Woman Nursing an Infant, circa 1900 (Box 17, Folder 1366)
      - The Redman's Fact; Drawing of American Indians in Canoes on the Rapids of a River, Probably the Niagara Falls, circa 1905 (Box 17, Folder 1367)
      - Kicking Bear, American Indian Man, circa 1905-1910 (Box 17, Folder 1368)
      - An Original Inhabitant and Some of Minnesota's Beautiful Lakes, circa 1908 (Box 17, Folder 1369)
      - Group of Sioux Indian Chiefs, circa 1908 (Box 17, Folder 1370)
      - Chief Iron Tail, Indian Squaws, and Papooses at Buffalo Bill's Wild West Show, circa 1909 (Box 17, Folder 1371)
      - A Navajo Blanket Weaver (No. 746), circa 1910 (Box 17, Folder 1372)
      - Buckskin Charlie, Ute Indian Man, circa 1912 (Box 17, Folder 1373)
- Printed Material and Press Kit, 1899-1975; Series VIII; 0.81; (4 boxes)
  Series VIII is organized into four subseries: Prints, Cigarette Cards, Playing Cards, and a Press Kit for The Shadow Catcher.
  This series consists chiefly of pictorial works produced by various printing processes. The series also includes a press kit for the documentary film The Shadow Catcher.
  - Prints
    Arranged by format and then by the creator or chronologically therein.